#### Contact

mr.core.hard@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/danielr-61a5b11a1 (LinkedIn) github.com/Reeves999 (Other)

### Top Skills

Customer Service Management Sales

#### Certifications

Configuration Management and the Cloud

Troubleshooting and Debugging Techniques

Crash Course on Python Introduction to Git and GitHub Certified Nursing Assistant

# **Daniel Reeves**

Developer/Dog Sitter Englewood

## Summary

Looking for an opportunity to learn

Tech is one of my hobbies and enjoyment in life. I adore it. For the past two years, I have been trying to understand and learn how to use technology to my benefit and for others. I know how to program proficiently in python and have basic knowledge of Java. Windows and Linux operating systems are very well. I already have five certifications with Google For IT Python Automation. I have tinkered with a Chromebook and was able to convert it into a Linux operating system without extensive hardware tools. I've been taking apart old laptops and seeing how I can use them or how they look. Mostly my skills are set for customer service and with people. I work well with others, even in stressful situations. At IKEA, I had to work in two departments due to short staffing issues. The main job in IKEA is to help the customer resolve their problems if the problems are way more significant than I'm authorized to do. I have resolutions take over the case. I have some warehouse experience from Amazon. I worked in a retirement home thinking I wanted to be a nurse when I did not. People tend to work based on validation for how good they worked. I don't tend to be that way. I'll look at the world where it needs to be more effective; I like to be a piece to make it more effective. Being lazy is not one of my virtues. I don't make excuses. I do better.

## Experience

Freelance Developer May 2022 - Present (1 month)

Build Software for a range of different applications.

Rover.com

Pet Sitter

May 2022 - Present (1 month)

I provide a services for pets. I take care of pets who want love and attention. If you would like to do a dog boarding. Here is my rover link. https://www.rover.com/sit/danr36590

Also a promo code for 20 off for first-time bookings.

#### **IKEA**

Customer Service Return Specialist July 2020 - May 2022 (1 year 11 months) Centennial, Colorado, United States

Amazon Web Services (AWS) Warehouse Associate August 2019 - July 2020 (1 year)

Panera Bread
Panera Associate
July 2017 - April 2019 (1 year 10 months)
Denver, Colorado, United States

Christian Living Communities
C.N.A
August 2018 - January 2019 (6 months)
Denver, Colorado, United States

Subway Sandwich Artist March 2017 - May 2017 (3 months) Denver, Colorado, United States

## Education

Cherry Creek High School High School Diploma, General Studies · (2014 - 2018)